("Another Night")
(upbeat dance music)
(upbeat techno music)
(upbeat dance techno music)
♪ Another night, another
dream, but always you ♪
♪ It's like a vision of
love that seems to be true ♪
♪ Another night, another
dream, but always you ♪
♪ In the night, I dream of love so true ♪
♪ Just another night,
another vision of love ♪
♪ You feel joy, you feel pain ♪
♪ 'Cause nothing will be the same ♪
♪ Just another night,
is all that it takes ♪
♪ To understand, the difference
between lovers and fakes ♪
♪ So baby, I talk talk, I talk to you ♪
♪ In the night, in your
dream, of love so true ♪
♪ I talk talk, I talk to you ♪
♪ In the night, in your
dream, of love so true ♪
♪ In the night, in my dreams ♪
♪ I'm in love with you, 'cause
you talk to me like lovers do ♪
♪ I feel joy, I feel pain,
'cause it's still the same ♪
♪ When the night is gone, I'll be alone ♪
♪ Another night, another
dream, but always you ♪
♪ It's like a vision of
love that seems to be true ♪
♪ Another night another
dream, but always you ♪
♪ In the night, I dream of love so true ♪
♪ Just another night, another
dream, another vision ♪
♪ Of love, with me ♪
♪ I'm here to set you free, I
am your lover, your brother ♪
♪ Hey sister let me cover,
your body with my love ♪
♪ Is with my lovin' just another ♪
♪ Vision of love, that seems to be true ♪
♪ All we do, all the things
that only lovers do ♪
♪ Vision of love, that seems to be true ♪
♪ All we do, all the things
that only lovers do ♪
♪ In the night, in my dreams ♪
♪ I'm in love with you, 'cause
you talk to me like lovers do ♪
♪ I feel joy, I feel pain,
'cause it's still the same ♪
♪ When the night is gone, I'll be alone ♪
♪ Another night, another
dream, but always you ♪
♪ It's like a vision of
love that seems to be true ♪
♪ Another night, another
dream, but always you ♪
♪ In the night, I dream of love so true ♪
♪ I talk talk, I talk
to you in the night ♪
♪ In your dream, of love so true ♪
♪ I talk talk, I talk
to you, in the night ♪
♪ In your dream, of love so true ♪
♪ In the night, in my dreams ♪
♪ I'm in love with you, 'cause
you talk to me like lovers do ♪
♪ I feel joy, I feel pain,
'cause it's still the same ♪
♪ When the night is gone, I'll be alone ♪
♪ Another night, another
dream, but always you ♪
♪ It's like a vision of
love that seems to be true ♪
♪ Another night, another
dream, but always you ♪
♪ In the night, I dream of love so true ♪